[
    {
        "Id": 1,
        "Question": "1|22|333",
        "Answer": 23212332,
        "Time": 6,
        "Weight": 3,
        "Difficult": 1
    },
    {
        "Id": 2,
        "Question": "11|222|333",
        "Answer": 22211333,
        "Time": 6,
        "Weight": 3,
        "Difficult": 1
    },
    {
        "Id": 3,
        "Question": "111|22|33",
        "Answer": 33111221,
        "Time": 6,
        "Weight": 3,
        "Difficult": 1
    },
    {
        "Id": 4,
        "Question": "2|33|11",
        "Answer": 13211233,
        "Time": 6,
        "Weight": 3,
        "Difficult": 1
    },
    {
        "Id": 5,
        "Question": "22|1|333",
        "Answer": 13332213,
        "Time": 6,
        "Weight": 3,
        "Difficult": 1
    },
    {
        "Id": 6,
        "Question": "222|111|33",
        "Answer": 33111222,
        "Time": 6,
        "Weight": 3,
        "Difficult": 1
    },
    {
        "Id": 7,
        "Question": "3|111|22",
        "Answer": 22311132,
        "Time": 6,
        "Weight": 3,
        "Difficult": 1
    },
    {
        "Id": 8,
        "Question": "33|22|11",
        "Answer": 11233122,
        "Time": 6,
        "Weight": 3,
        "Difficult": 1
    },
    {
        "Id": 9,
        "Question": "333|22|11",
        "Answer": 21223331,
        "Time": 6,
        "Weight": 3,
        "Difficult": 1
    },
    {
        "Id": 10,
        "Question": "1|2|333",
        "Answer": 33123133,
        "Time": 6,
        "Weight": 3,
        "Difficult": 1
    },
    {
        "Id": 11,
        "Question": "1|22|333",
        "Answer": 23212332,
        "Time": 5,
        "Weight": 2,
        "Difficult": 2
    },
    {
        "Id": 12,
        "Question": "11|222|333",
        "Answer": 22211333,
        "Time": 5,
        "Weight": 2,
        "Difficult": 2
    },
    {
        "Id": 13,
        "Question": "111|22|33",
        "Answer": 33111221,
        "Time": 5,
        "Weight": 2,
        "Difficult": 2
    },
    {
        "Id": 14,
        "Question": "2|33|11",
        "Answer": 13211233,
        "Time": 5,
        "Weight": 2,
        "Difficult": 2
    },
    {
        "Id": 15,
        "Question": "22|1|333",
        "Answer": 13332213,
        "Time": 5,
        "Weight": 2,
        "Difficult": 2
    },
    {
        "Id": 16,
        "Question": "222|111|33",
        "Answer": 33111222,
        "Time": 5,
        "Weight": 2,
        "Difficult": 2
    },
    {
        "Id": 17,
        "Question": "3|111|22",
        "Answer": 22311132,
        "Time": 5,
        "Weight": 2,
        "Difficult": 2
    },
    {
        "Id": 18,
        "Question": "33|22|11",
        "Answer": 11233122,
        "Time": 5,
        "Weight": 2,
        "Difficult": 2
    },
    {
        "Id": 19,
        "Question": "333|22|11",
        "Answer": 21223331,
        "Time": 5,
        "Weight": 2,
        "Difficult": 2
    },
    {
        "Id": 20,
        "Question": "1|2|333",
        "Answer": 33123133,
        "Time": 5,
        "Weight": 2,
        "Difficult": 2
    },
    {
        "Id": 21,
        "Question": "1|22|333",
        "Answer": 23212332,
        "Time": 4,
        "Weight": 1,
        "Difficult": 3
    },
    {
        "Id": 22,
        "Question": "11|222|333",
        "Answer": 22211333,
        "Time": 4,
        "Weight": 1,
        "Difficult": 3
    },
    {
        "Id": 23,
        "Question": "111|22|33",
        "Answer": 33111221,
        "Time": 4,
        "Weight": 1,
        "Difficult": 3
    },
    {
        "Id": 24,
        "Question": "2|33|11",
        "Answer": 13211233,
        "Time": 4,
        "Weight": 1,
        "Difficult": 3
    },
    {
        "Id": 25,
        "Question": "22|1|333",
        "Answer": 13332213,
        "Time": 4,
        "Weight": 1,
        "Difficult": 3
    },
    {
        "Id": 26,
        "Question": "222|111|33",
        "Answer": 33111222,
        "Time": 4,
        "Weight": 1,
        "Difficult": 3
    },
    {
        "Id": 27,
        "Question": "3|111|22",
        "Answer": 22311132,
        "Time": 4,
        "Weight": 1,
        "Difficult": 3
    },
    {
        "Id": 28,
        "Question": "33|22|11",
        "Answer": 11233122,
        "Time": 4,
        "Weight": 1,
        "Difficult": 3
    },
    {
        "Id": 29,
        "Question": "333|22|11",
        "Answer": 21223331,
        "Time": 4,
        "Weight": 1,
        "Difficult": 3
    },
    {
        "Id": 30,
        "Question": "1|2|333",
        "Answer": 33123133,
        "Time": 4,
        "Weight": 1,
        "Difficult": 3
    }
]